JUDE CLARK

Duluth, GA 30097

Phone: 678-825-JUDE (5833) | Email: judeclark2019@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jude-clark-89262634/ GitHub: github.com/judeclark19 | Portfolio: https://jude-clark.netlify.app/

SUMMARY

Full-Stack web developer with experience in client relations, administration, and systems analysis. A natural problem solver with excellent language skills; including listening, comprehension, and clear expression. Excels in a position that involves solving both daily problems with a high level of detail as well as larger, more complex issues.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Technologies: MongoDB, Node JS, MySQL, Sass, React JS

PROJECTS

Virtual Menorah - https://spacial-fray-menorah.netlify.app

Inspired by the fact that Hanukkah will be celebrated over Zoom this year, here's a virtual Menorah you can light on screen.

Animated Portfolio - https://spacial-fray-capture.netlify.app

A mock-portfolio website that heavily features animations powered by framer-motion.

Let's Roll - https://gt-lets-roll.herokuapp.com

Final Bootcamp project; a social media app for quad skaters to share information about where and how to skate.

EXPERIENCE

Executive Assistant to the CEO

August 2018 - October 2019

Jar House (Atlanta, GA)

- Assisted with ETL of property data for company-wide shift to SalesForce.
- Built custom SalesForce report types to manipulate complex object relationships and produce reports for various departments' needs.

Patron Services Manager

November 2014 - June 2018

Seraphic Fire (Miami, FL)

- Served as the primary point of contact for all external communications, handling all patron interactions with the highest level of professionalism.
- Managed SalesForce database of all donations, donors, and ticket buyers. Assisted with data migration through two complete software transitions of a database containing about 30,000 contacts.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp Certificate — Georgia Institute of Technology AUGUST 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

Bachelor of Music, Music Composition — *University of South Carolina* AUGUST 2010 - MAY 2014, Summa cum laude